From incredible passion grows incredible beauty.
A Little Chaos is a drama, romance film directed by Alan Rickman.
A landscape gardener is hired by famous architect Le Nôtre to
construct the grand gardens at the palace of Versailles.
As the two work on the palace, they find themselves drawn to each other and
are thrown into rivalries within the court of King Louis XIV.
Sabine De Barra, played by Kate Winslet.
Andre Le Notre, played by Matthias Schoenaerts.
King Louis XIV, played by Alan Rickman.
Philippe, Duc d'Orleans, played by Stanley Tucci.
Madame Le Notre, played by Helen McCrory.
Thierry Duras, played by Steven Waddington.
A Little Chaos is a 2014 British period drama film directed by Alan Rickman, based on a story
conceived by Alison Deegan, who co-wrote the screenplay with Rickman and Jeremy Brock.
It stars Kate Winslet, Matthias Schoenaerts, Rickman, Stanley Tucci, Helen
McCrory, Steven Waddington, Jennifer Ehle and Rupert Penry-Jones.
It was financed by Lionsgate UK and produced by BBC Films.
The second film directed by Rickman, after his 1997 debut The Winter Guest, and the last before his death in 2016, it
was also the second collaboration of Rickman and Winslet after their 1995 film Sense and Sensibility.
Production took place in London in mid-2013, and it premiered as the closing night film
at the 2014 Toronto International Film Festival on 13 September 2014.
The film explores themes of adultery, infidelity,
jealousy, france, paris, france.
The tone is emotional.